

CONTACT

- (+977-9868067264
- ☐ dammar@xdezo.com | dammar2057@gmail.com
- ◆ 33700, Pokhara-7, Ratna Chowk, Kaski, Nepal
- www.dammarkhadayat.com.np

EDUCATION

SLC - 2072

Shree Deveshwary Secondary School, Deulekh, Bajhang, Nepal

+2 | Management | Business Studies: 2074

Little Buddha Academy , Mahendranagar, Kanchanpur, Nepal

Bachelors | Bachelor of Computer Application

LA GRANDEE International College, Pokhara, Kaski , Nepal

CERTIFICATIONS

- Full Stack Web Development with PHP laravel Course From XDezo Technologies Pvt. Ltd
- Graphics Design Masterclass Course

SKILLS

Hard Skills

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap
- PHP, Intermediate Laravel
- MYSQL, SQL
- git and github
- WordPress Development
- Graphics Design
- Project Management

Soft Skills

- Observation
- Decision making
- Communication
- Multi-tasking
- Team Work

LANGUAGE

English Nepali Hindi

Dammar Khadayat

Web Developer

Profile

I am a qualified and professional web developer with many years of experience in web design & development, graphics Design, WordPress development, and social media management. I have strong project management skills, and creative, analytical skills and good team leadership. My passion lies in learning about the latest technologies and implementing them.

Professional Experience

2019 - 2020

XDezo Technologies Pvt. Ltd

Jr. Frontend Developer

I worked as a Frontend Developer based on core code web designer using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap . I developed many project such as school website, Portfolio , and ECommerce etc. I was full time employee.

2020 - Present

XDezo Technologies Pvt. Ltd., Pokhara-7, Ratna Chowk, Kaski, Nepal

Project Supervisor | Web Developer

I am working as a Web Developer based on core code web designer using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, and core PHP. I developed many projects such as the school website, Portfolio, E-Commerce, etc. And I handle standard projects such as school projects etc. And good team leader and direction.

2021 - Present

XDezo Academy, Pokhara-7, Ratna Chowk, Kaski, Nepal

Academic Coordinator | Instructor

I am working as an academic coordinator at XDezo Academy. I am the instructor of the Full Stack Web Development with PHP Laravel course in full time. Currently, I have been teaching frontend and backend web development.

2021 - present

XDezo Academy, Pokhara-7, Ratna Chowk, Kaski, Nepal **Internship Supervisor**

I am working as a supervisor of Web Development and Graphics Design. I totally handle all tasks, designs, projects, and their performance. I have been provided good guidance and direction and led to them.

Scholarship

Full Scholarship from Pokhara University - 2018

for the Batchelor of Computer Application (BCA) Program